<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Game Loid</title>
    <link>https://game-loid.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Game Loid</description>
    <image>
      <url>https://game-loid.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</url>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/%3Clink%20or%20path%20of%20image%20for%20opengraph,%20twitter-cards%3E</link>
    </image>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://game-loid.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title> Guide to Keira and Sebastian Jet in Hero Wars Mobile - META Episode 001</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/keira-pvp-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/keira-pvp-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the jungle! In this guide, we will explain the powerful and interesting combination of Keira and Sebastian Jet in Hero Wars Mobile. This dynamic duo is known for their incredible damage output, making them a force to be reckoned with in guild wars and crossrad elements.
First, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about Keira&amp;rsquo;s abilities. Her basic attack, &amp;ldquo;Dancing Blades,&amp;rdquo; is devastating. It not only deals damage to the enemy in front of her, but also increases her damage output for a short period of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Where to Use Attacks in Guild Wars - A Comprehensive Strategy Guide | Hero Wars</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-silver-guild-war-trophy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-silver-guild-war-trophy/</guid>
      <description>Guild Wars is a crucial aspect of Hero Wars gameplay and requires careful planning and strategy to ensure victory. In this article, we will discuss the best practices for using your attacks in Guild Wars and provide helpful tips for beginners.
Identifying Your Specialty The first step in determining where to use your attacks is to identify your specialty. Are you more skilled at attacking titans or heroes? This self-awareness will help you assess your strengths and weaknesses during battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars — Arachne Maya: The Unbeatable DPS Combo?</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/is-maya-or-the-better-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/is-maya-or-the-better-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Hero Wars is a popular mobile game that offers a wide variety of heroes for players to choose from. Today, we will discuss the powerful combo of Arachne and Maya, two beloved heroes in the game. This duo has captured the attention of players due to their exceptional synergy and high damage output. In this article, we will delve into the details of Arachne and Maya, examine their abilities, and explore why they make the perfect pairing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ID Inspector: Track Any Attacker by Inspecting Game Files - Rise of Kingdoms ROK</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-how-to-look-at-someones-city/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-how-to-look-at-someones-city/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the popular mobile game Rise of Kingdoms, it can be frustrating when your old farm account is attacked by someone who changes their name and location after the attack. Finding the attacker within the game becomes nearly impossible. However, in this article, we will discuss a clever trick that can help you obtain the attacker&amp;rsquo;s govern ID, even if they have changed their name, picture, and location. By inspecting specific game files stored on your phone, you can gather valuable information that is not readily available in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Your Heroes Will Have Longer Lives with Optimized Stats | Hero Wars: Alliance</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-stats/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this episode of Guardian&amp;rsquo;s Guidebook, we will delve into the importance of armor and magic defense in Hero Wars battles. These stats play a crucial role in reducing the damage your guardians receive during combat. Additionally, we will explore how these stats interact with special stats like armor penetration and magic penetration. By understanding and optimizing these stats, you will significantly enhance the longevity of your heroes in battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Get Rich in Epic Seven - The Ultimate Guide to Maximizing Gold Income</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-which-hunt-to-farm/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-which-hunt-to-farm/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you looking to become incredibly wealthy in Epic Seven? Do you dream of showcasing your one billion gold badge to your friends and proving just how much you&amp;rsquo;ve achieved in the game? Look no further, because this guide is here to help you achieve your financial goals. In this article, we will compare the benefits of farming in the Hunt and Unrecorded History modes during a buff event, so that you can make an informed decision based on your specific needs.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars Dark Star: A Controversial DPS Hero with Potential</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/dark-star-hero-wars-stats/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/dark-star-hero-wars-stats/</guid>
      <description>Dark Star, once a beloved hero in Hero Wars, has recently undergone a controversial transformation with her new health skin. In this article, we will delve into the details of Dark Star&amp;rsquo;s abilities, discuss her potential, and analyze how the presence of Sebastian, a powerful hero, hinders her effectiveness. We will also explore the necessity of a rework for Dark Star and the practicality of using her in battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Minecraft Nebula Wars - Conquer the Galaxy in Skywars Server</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/minecraft-nebula-wars-server/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/minecraft-nebula-wars-server/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to Minecraft Nebula Wars, a thrilling multiplayer experience where players battle it out in the sky. In this game, your objective is to destroy the enemy team&amp;rsquo;s monuments while eliminating opposing players. With intense PvP combat and strategic gameplay, Nebula Wars is sure to keep you hooked for hours. Join us today in the interstellar battleground and show off your skills!
Key Points:
Joining the Nebula Wars Lobby: To join the Nebula Wars lobby, simply type &amp;ldquo;/join&amp;rdquo; in the chat and select lobby three.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Diablo 4 - A Comprehensive Guide to the Interactive Map of Diablo 4 World</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/diablo-4-map-size/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 14 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/diablo-4-map-size/</guid>
      <description>Diablo 4 is an upcoming action role-playing game that has gained significant attention from gamers around the world. As the highly anticipated release date approaches, players are eager to explore and navigate the massive world of Diablo 4. In this article, we will take an in-depth look at the full interactive map of Diablo 4 and how it can help players strategize their gameplay.
Understanding the Interactive Map The interactive map of Diablo 4, available on d4planner.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [🔥Best of the Best🔥] Empires &amp; Puzzles Introduces Exciting New Hero League Event</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-new-event-heroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-new-event-heroes/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In a recent update for Empires &amp;amp; Puzzles, a popular mobile game, a new event called Hero League has been introduced. This PvP-based event adds a fresh twist to the gameplay and promises to keep players entertained for hours. In this article, we will delve into the details of the Hero League event, discussing its format, scoring system, and rewards.
Hero League Format
The Hero League event is a raid-based PvP event that is played in a league format.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 5 Little-known Tips for Winning Offensive Raids in Empires and Puzzles 2019</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-raid-tips/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-raid-tips/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing five little-known tips for winning offensive raids in Empires and Puzzles 2019. These tips will help you build the correct team, focus on the middle, assess your opponents&amp;rsquo; defensive heroes, kill heroes efficiently, and prioritize your moves and specials. By following these tips, you will increase your chances of success in raids.
Building the Correct Team One important aspect of winning offensive raids is building the correct team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 99% of Players Don&#39;t Know This! 4 Pro Artifact Tips to Master King&#39;s Raid</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-best-artifact/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-best-artifact/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to this article where we will be discussing four pro artifact tips that 99% of players don&amp;rsquo;t know about in the popular game King&amp;rsquo;s Raid. As an expert copywriter in the gaming industry, I want to share these valuable tips with you to help you master the game and improve your gameplay. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in!
Tip 1: Take Advantage of Sub Stat Charms The first tip we have for you is to take advantage of sub stat charms in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Heir of Light Indonesia: Understanding the Different DPS Categories</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/heir-of-light-tier-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/heir-of-light-tier-list/</guid>
      <description>DPS (Damage Per Second) in Heir of Light is an important aspect of the game that players need to understand in order to optimize their gameplay. In this article, we will explore the various categories of DPS servants and how to identify them. By gaining a clear understanding of these categories, players can strategize their team compositions and improve their performance in the game.
Categories of DPS Servants There are five categories of DPS servants in Heir of Light.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Rise of Kingdoms Beginners Guide 2023: Tips for New &#43; Returning Players</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-new-player-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-new-player-guide/</guid>
      <description>Rise of Kingdoms is a popular strategy game that has attracted many players, both new and returning. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for a guide to help you navigate the game and make the most out of your experience, you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover everything you need to know as a new player in Rise of Kingdoms, or if you&amp;rsquo;re returning to the game after a long break.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TALES OF ERIN Crafted Tier IV Crit Gun Review - A Guide to Maximizing Gameplay</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/tales-of-erin-tier-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/tales-of-erin-tier-list/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the highly sought-after tier IV crit gun in the popular mobile game, TALES OF ERIN. This powerful weapon provides a significant boost to team crit damage and can greatly enhance your gameplay experience. We will delve into the details of this weapon, its benefits, and how you can optimize its usage in your team. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
Key Points The tier IV crit gun is a highly coveted weapon in TALES OF ERIN due to its ability to significantly increase team crit damage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Top 5 Support Heroes Every Account Should Have - King’s Raid Character Guide**</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-character-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-character-guide/</guid>
      <description>Are you an avid player of the popular mobile game King&amp;rsquo;s Raid? If so, then you know the importance of having strong support heroes in your arsenal. In this article, we will discuss the top 5 support heroes that every account should have. These heroes will greatly enhance your gameplay and help you achieve victory in battles. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and discover these powerful heroes!
Support Hero #1: Gym First on our list is Gym, a support hero known for his healing abilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BEST Incursion Raid Teams to Build: Power Levels &amp; Nodes to SIM in MARVEL Strike Force</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/msf-best-raid-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/msf-best-raid-team/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this video, we will discuss the best incursion raid teams to build and how to master them in MARVEL Strike Force. We will explore various synergies and teams that have been proven effective in these raids. The goal is to help you understand the power levels and nodes to SIM so that you can progress efficiently. Additionally, we will share some strategies that have led to high damage output and success in these raids.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven: Upgrading Your Sanctuary and Maximizing Breath of Orbis Usage</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-breath-of-orbis-usage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-breath-of-orbis-usage/</guid>
      <description>In this guide, we will discuss the importance of the Breath of Orbis in Epic Seven and how to obtain them. The Breath of Orbis is a crucial resource used to upgrade your sanctuary and unlock various bonuses and rewards. As we delve into the depths of this topic, we will explore different aspects of the game and provide expert advice on how to maximize your Breath of Orbis usage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Banner Lords: The Faction&#39;s Hidden Gems | Raid Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-best-banner-lords/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-best-banner-lords/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with the Banner Lords faction in Raid Shadow Legends? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. While this faction may not have the easiest Champions to work with, there are some hidden gems that can make your journey through the faction wars much easier. In this article, we will explore the different bosses, discuss the strategies to defeat them, and analyze the available Champions in the faction. Plus, we&amp;rsquo;ll even attempt to beat the stage 21 boss without any legendaries or crazy gear.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> BEST 3v3 TEAMS RANKED: From Offense to Defense - June 2023</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/best-mid-game-grand-arena-teams-swgoh/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/best-mid-game-grand-arena-teams-swgoh/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In the ever-changing landscape of Galaxy of Heroes, 3v3 battles have made their return, and in this video, we will rank all the best 3v3 teams from the top-tier to the worst. This ranking is based on a comprehensive analysis of the current state of the game, taking into account different rosters, counters, and strategies. We will also discuss the ideal placement and usage of each character to help you optimize your teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars - Best Ways to Utilize Guild War Trophies: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-obtain-silver-guild-war-trophies-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-obtain-silver-guild-war-trophies-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Guild War Trophies are an important aspect of the popular mobile game Hero Wars. These trophies are obtained through participating in wars and vary depending on the league you are in. In this article, we will explore the best ways to utilize guild war trophies and maximize their benefits.
Key Points: 1.Guild war trophies are earned in wars every week and vary according to your league (gold, silver, bronze). Bronze league and qualifying players receive bronze trophies, silver league players receive silver trophies, and gold league players obtain gold trophies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Build a Balanced Keira Team in Hero Wars</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-keira-pure/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 11 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-keira-pure/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss how to build an effective Keira team in the popular game Hero Wars. Specifically, we will focus on a team lineup that includes Keira, Nebula, and Orion. This lineup is known for its balance and effectiveness against various types of teams.
The Core Lineup: Keira, Nebula, and Orion The core of this team consists of three heroes: Keira, Nebula, and Orion. Keira is a hero with high armor penetration, while Orion has very high magic penetration.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>  Exploring the Painful Realism of Virtual Reality with Haptic Suits</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/anime-and-videogame-jackets/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/anime-and-videogame-jackets/</guid>
      <description>H1: Exploring the Painful Realism of Virtual Reality with Haptic Suits
Virtual reality (VR) has come a long way in recent years, offering immersive experiences that transport users to new worlds and provide incredibly realistic sensations. But what if you could not only see and hear, but also feel the impact of every punch, shot, or sword strike in a game? That&amp;rsquo;s exactly what haptic suits aim to do - providing users with a true sense of pain in virtual reality.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven: Maximizing Your Sanctuary Improvements for Maximum Rewards</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/breath-of-orbis-epic-seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/breath-of-orbis-epic-seven/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the world of Epic Seven, the Sanctuary plays an important role in providing players with valuable resources and rewards. In this article, we will explore the various buildings within the Sanctuary and discuss how to make them more efficient in order to maximize your rewards. Whether you are a free player or a seasoned veteran, these tips and strategies will help you make the most of your Epic Seven experience.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Marvel Strike Force Blitz Team - Kingpin &#43; Crossbones</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-strike-force-best-team-with-crossbones/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 10 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-strike-force-best-team-with-crossbones/</guid>
      <description>Are you looking to dominate the Blitz mode in Marvel Strike Force? Well, look no further because we have the ultimate team for you - Kingpin and Crossbones! This team composition is guaranteed to give you insane damage and secure victory in every battle. In this article, we will delve into the mechanics of this team and how to maximize their potential. So, gear up and get ready to conquer Blitz mode!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Jet vs Fafnir Comparison: Which Hero is More Powerful in Hero Wars Mobile?</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/jet-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/jet-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back Hero Power Players to Eagle Eye Gaming! In today&amp;rsquo;s video, we will discuss the importance of building Jet and compare Jet with Fafnir, along with other alternative support characters in Hero Wars Mobile. The emergence of Fafnir as a viable alternative has created a debate among players, so let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the details.
Why Did We Build Jet Before Fafnir&amp;rsquo;s Release? Jet was a popular choice in team compositions because of his critical ability, which grants a chance for double physical damage to physical attackers, even if they don&amp;rsquo;t possess innate critical ability themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Role of the Dark Vampire Lord in Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-get-dark-vampire-lord-summoners-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-get-dark-vampire-lord-summoners-war/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will delve into the intriguing question of why the dark vampire lord was introduced in Summoners War and what purpose it serves in the game. Many players have wondered about the significance of this unique character and how it fits into their gameplay strategies. We will explore the reasons behind its inclusion and shed light on its usefulness in various aspects of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Are Walkthroughs and Guides Beneficial or Detrimental to Gaming?</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/games-for-guides/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/games-for-guides/</guid>
      <description>In the world of video games, it&amp;rsquo;s not uncommon to get stuck and feel lost. We&amp;rsquo;ve all been there at some point, and many of us have turned to walkthroughs and guides for help. But are these resources really a good thing? In this article, we will explore the advantages and disadvantages of using walkthroughs and guides in gaming and discuss how they can affect our overall gaming experience. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and see if these tools are helpful or if they hinder our enjoyment.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RAID: Shatterbones Champion Spotlight - A Guide to a Top-Tier Epic in RAID: Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/shatter-bones-raid-shadow-legends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/shatter-bones-raid-shadow-legends/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will be taking a closer look at Shatterbones, a top-tier epic champion in RAID: Shadow Legends. We will explore his kit and abilities, as well as how to effectively gear and use him in different game modes.
Overview of Shatterbones Shatterbones is an epic champion who possesses incredible abilities that make him a force to be reckoned with on the battlefield. His kit allows him to control turn meters, deal damage, and support his team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Top 10 DPS Servants in Heir of Light - Unleash the Power of the Best Tank</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/best-tank-in-heir-of-light/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 08 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/best-tank-in-heir-of-light/</guid>
      <description>In the world of Heir of Light, there are countless powerful servants to choose from. But when it comes to dealing massive damage, only a select few stand out as the best of the best. In this article, we will explore the top 10 DPS (Damage Per Second) servants that can make you say &amp;ldquo;WOW!&amp;rdquo; Prepare to be amazed as we delve into their skills, abilities, and why they deserve a spot on your team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> FINAL FANTASY XVI: The Epic Tale of Dion Lesage&#39;s Journey [4K]</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/dione-ffxiv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/dione-ffxiv/</guid>
      <description>In the highly anticipated game FINAL FANTASY XVI, players are taken on a thrilling adventure through the eyes of Dion Lesage. This article takes a deep dive into the character of Dion Lesage and his journey through the game, exploring the key cutscenes that players will encounter.
Introduction to Dion Lesage Dion Lesage is a central character in FINAL FANTASY XVI, known for his bravery and loyalty to the Empire of Sandburg.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gems of War | The Tired Alchemist Lab | Herald of Blight | Daemon Gameplay ft. Famine</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/gems-of-war-herald-of-chaos/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/gems-of-war-herald-of-chaos/</guid>
      <description>Gems of War is a popular game that challenges players to strategize and battle their way to victory. In this article, we will be focusing on the new troop introduced in the game&amp;rsquo;s soul forge, Famine. Additionally, we will discuss the Herald of Blight, a recently released troop that offers unique abilities. These troops are particularly useful for specific battles, making them valuable assets in your gameplay.
Introducing Famine and the Herald of Blight Famine is a powerful troop that can greatly impact battles in Gems of War.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sanctuary &#43; Breath of Orbis - How and Where to Use?? - What to Upgrade? - Epic Seven Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-get-breath-of-orbis/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-get-breath-of-orbis/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this guide, we will be discussing the sanctuary and how to use your Breath of Orbis effectively in the game Epic Seven. For newer players, the sanctuary and the Breath of Orbis can be confusing, but with this guide, you&amp;rsquo;ll have a better understanding of where and how to use them.
What is the Sanctuary and Breath of Orbis? The sanctuary in Epic Seven is a place where you can upgrade buildings using the Breath of Orbis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mastering ATOM RPG: Infinite Move, God Mode, and One Hit Kill Scripts - Series 2</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/atom-rpg-cheat-engine/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 07 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/atom-rpg-cheat-engine/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to a comprehensive guide on how to master ATOM RPG. In this article, we will delve into the second part of the series by Garik 66 from Gamehacklab YouTube channel. We will explore the scripts for infinite move, god mode, and one hit kill and learn how to use them effectively in the game. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
The Initial Setup In this episode, Garik 66 begins by checking the previous series, where he successfully implemented the scripts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [Blade and Soul] Soulboost Season 3: Step by Step Guide For New &amp; Returning Players</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/blade-and-soul-leveling/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/blade-and-soul-leveling/</guid>
      <description>Are you a new or returning player of Blade and Soul? In this comprehensive guide, we will walk you through the process of completing your Soulboost quickly and efficiently. Our step-by-step instructions will cover all the quests and rewards that you need to know about, so you can level up your character and obtain powerful gear. Get ready to embark on an epic adventure in the world of Blade and Soul.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 17 Armor Shreds in 1 Battle? Let the Cheese Begin! Sector 5 Feats Are Easy!</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/galaxy-of-heroes-armor-shred/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/galaxy-of-heroes-armor-shred/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Welcome back to another episode of Galaxy of Heroes! In this video, we will be tackling Sector 5 of Conquest and focusing on completing the Feats for this sector. We have some exciting strategies to share with you, so let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in!
Sector 5 Feats
In Sector 5, there are four Feats that we need to complete:
Unguarded: Win 14 battles with no tanks in your squad. Armor Up: Gain defense up 40 times in one battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gems of War Raid Boss: Unbelievably Easy Strategy for Massive Rewards</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/gems-of-war-mythic-boss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/gems-of-war-mythic-boss/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss an ultra-powerful team strategy that will turn the Gems of War Raid Boss battles into a walk in the park. We will provide step-by-step instructions on how to build this team and also share some helpful tips to maximize your rewards. By following this strategy, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to conquer the Raid Boss battles with ease and reap the benefits.
Before we dive into the team strategy, let&amp;rsquo;s start by mentioning some important tools you&amp;rsquo;ll need for this battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Get UW and UT Fast? - King&#39;s Raid Indonesia</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-ut/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-ut/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will discuss the ways to quickly acquire Unique Weapon (UW) and Unique Treasure (UT) in the popular game King&amp;rsquo;s Raid. As a player, it is common to desire instant progress and power without spending real money. We will explore different methods and strategies to achieve this goal while maximizing your in-game resources.
Method 1: Swipe for a Faster Progress
If you are willing to spend money on the game, promotions and special events can provide a significant advantage.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Tales of Erin: New Update Introduces Soul Spirit and Water Team Power</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/tales-of-erin-soul-spirit/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/tales-of-erin-soul-spirit/</guid>
      <description>Scion Storm Shares Exciting Details on the Latest Features In a recent video, Scion Storm dives into the exciting new update for Tales of Erin. The update brings significant changes to the UI and introduces the long-awaited Soul Spirit feature. Additionally, Scion Storm discusses the incredible power of the Water Team and its potential in battles. This article will cover the key points from the video and provide a comprehensive overview of the new update.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Much Money Have I Spent on Blade &amp; Soul?</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-much-money-have-i-spent-on-blade-and-soul/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-much-money-have-i-spent-on-blade-and-soul/</guid>
      <description>Blade &amp;amp; Soul is a popular online game that has captured the attention of many players around the world. But have you ever wondered how much money you have spent on the game? In this article, we will dive into the purchase history of a Blade &amp;amp; Soul player to find out exactly how much money they have spent. Be prepared, as the numbers might shock you!
Introduction Blade &amp;amp; Soul is an online game that has gained a strong following since its release.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kingdom Teleport, Ice Trash, and War Wolf Details: A Comprehensive Analysis - King of Avalon</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/king-of-avalon-teleport/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/king-of-avalon-teleport/</guid>
      <description>Kingdom teleportation, ice trash, and War Wolf details are hot topics in the King of Avalon community. As a Chinese game developed by a Chinese developer, King of Avalon is dominated by Chinese players. In this article, we will dive into the recent discussions and announcements surrounding these features. We&amp;rsquo;ll also explore the controversy surrounding the game&amp;rsquo;s favoritism towards Chinese players and the potential release of new equipment. So, let&amp;rsquo;s get started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Guide to the Top 50 Must-Have Promotions to 6 &amp; 7 Red Stars in Marvel Strike Force Q1/Q2 2023</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-strike-force-red-stars/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-strike-force-red-stars/</guid>
      <description>Marvel Strike Force players, listen up! There&amp;rsquo;s an unbelievable offer that you need to know about. In this article, we will delve into the details of this offer and discuss the best characters to use gold promotion credits on. We will also explore how these characters hold value in the future. Stay tuned as we reveal the characters we have already promoted to red stars.
But first, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the offer itself.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> I Got Tier 3 Artemis Skin In Less Than 8 minutes! Brawlhalla Battle Pass Season 5</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/all-skins-for-artemis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/all-skins-for-artemis/</guid>
      <description>Brawlhalla Battle Pass Season 5 is finally here, and it&amp;rsquo;s space-themed, which is super exciting. In this video, we will be diving into the battle pass track and showcasing how to obtain the Tier 3 Artemis Skin in less than 8 minutes. The new season brings with it various rewards such as the Event Horizon Artemis skin, an edge of existence podium, a unique sidekick, and a cosmos avatar. We will discuss all these exciting rewards and guide you through the process of obtaining them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> King&#39;s Raid - Fallen Frey: An In-Depth Analysis of Her Skills and Abilities</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-frey-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-frey-build/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be taking an in-depth look at Fallen Frey, a character in the popular mobile game King&amp;rsquo;s Raid. Fallen Frey is a versatile hero who excels in healing and providing support to her team. We will explore all of her skills and abilities, as well as different builds and strategies for optimal gameplay.
Tainted Angel - A Mana-Hungry Hero One of the key aspects of Fallen Frey&amp;rsquo;s gameplay is her mana cost and consumption.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Red&#39;s Full Team Explained: A Comprehensive Guide to Red&#39;s Pokémon Adventures</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/the-adventures-of-red-walkthrough/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/the-adventures-of-red-walkthrough/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Pokémon Adventures is an iconic manga series that follows the thrilling journey of Pokémon trainers as they embark on epic quests. In this article, we will explore the full team of the original main character, Red. From his first ever Pokémon to his formidable squad of companions, we will delve into the intricacies of Red&amp;rsquo;s team. Join us as we unravel the mysteries and uncover the strengths of each member.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> URUTAN UPGRADE HERO YANG BENAR ‼️ - HERO WARS MOBILE – A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-max-hero-level/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 04 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-max-hero-level/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss the correct order of upgrading your heroes in the popular mobile game, Hero Wars. Upgrading your heroes is crucial for strengthening your team and improving your chances of winning battles. There are several key points to consider when upgrading your heroes, and we will cover them in detail to ensure you fully understand the process.
Importance of Stars The first and most important aspect to consider when upgrading your heroes is their star rating.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Super Easy Rerolling in AFK Arena**</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rerolling-in-afkarena/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rerolling-in-afkarena/</guid>
      <description>Written by: [Your Name]
Introduction In this article, we will be discussing a new feature in AFK Arena that allows players to reroll easily on new servers. This feature is ideal for players who enjoy creating alt accounts or for those who want to keep up with the newest servers. We will explain how this feature works, the benefits of rerolling, and discuss potential future improvements.
The New Rerolling Feature The new rerolling feature in AFK Arena allows players to skip the tutorial and start the game directly at stage 2-4.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Easily Clear Brave Trial Nightmare Mode in Idle Heroes</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/idle-heroes-brave-trial-how-to/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/idle-heroes-brave-trial-how-to/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss a strategy to easily clear Brave Trial Nightmare mode in the popular game Idle Heroes. Brave Trial can be a challenging mode to conquer, but with the right team setup and strategy, you can achieve victory and earn valuable rewards. We will provide step-by-step instructions and tips to help you succeed in this challenging game mode.
Key Points Use a strong hero, such as Ticks, to increase your chances of success Collect blessings and use them strategically Focus on specific rounds to optimize your team&amp;rsquo;s performance Avoid leveling up multiple heroes to keep your power level low Consider using heroes like Garuda and Inosuke for their healing abilities Step-by-Step Process Step 1: Build a Strong Team with Ticks Ticks is an essential hero for navigating Brave Trial Nightmare mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> New Primal Dragons and Treasure Hunt Event in Dragon Mania Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/amulet-of-treasure-finding/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/amulet-of-treasure-finding/</guid>
      <description>Dragon Mania Legends has just released a new treasure hunt event, along with the addition of powerful new dragons called Primal Dragons. In this article, we will take an in-depth look at the treasure hunt event, how to participate, and the rewards you can earn.
The Treasure Hunt Event The treasure hunt event in Dragon Mania Legends is an exciting opportunity to collect amulets and exchange them for special dragons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> [AFK ARENA] Enhancing Mythic&#43; Gear: How to Obtain and Its Benefits</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/afk-arena-how-do-you-enhance-gear/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/afk-arena-how-do-you-enhance-gear/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will delve into the world of AFK Arena and explore the process of enhancing Mythic+ gear. Many players may be unfamiliar with this feature and may wonder how to obtain it and how strong it actually is. We will guide you through the steps of obtaining and upgrading this gear, as well as discuss its significance in the game. So let&amp;rsquo;s jump in and discover the wonders of Mythic+ gear in AFK Arena!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Everlook WoW Private Server Client Download Instructional Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/download-private-servers/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/download-private-servers/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you new to the private server scene and want to know how to get started? Look no further! In this article, we will guide you through the step-by-step process of downloading the Everlook WoW Private Server client. By the end of this guide, you will have everything set up and be ready to play on the private server when it officially launches.
Step 1: Visit the Everlook Website Before we begin, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that the developers estimate a November launch for the server.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Guide: GOD MODE Berserker Build, Masteries &amp; Tips | RAID Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-berserker-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 02 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-berserker-build/</guid>
      <description>Unlock the full potential of the Berserker champion with this detailed guide on how to build him for optimal performance in different areas of the game.
Introduction In this article, we will delve into the world of RAID Shadow Legends and focus on a highly underrated champion, the Berserker. Often overlooked by players, the Berserker has the potential to excel as a farmer, solo champion, and nuker. We will explore his abilities, gear requirements, masteries, and showcase his capabilities in various game modes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars — How to Obtain All 30 Titan Totems for Guaranteed Success!</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/guaranteed-totem-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/guaranteed-totem-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the world of Hero Wars, acquiring powerful Titan Totems is crucial for success. These unique artifacts enhance your heroes&amp;rsquo; abilities, making them formidable in battle. However, the process of obtaining these totems has undergone some changes recently. In this article, we will explore the new guaranteed totem system and provide you with valuable insights on how to obtain all 30 titan totems.
The Guaranteed Totem System Previously, players had to rely on random chance to obtain titan totems.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How does CASSIE compare to KARAMBIT in Summoners War: Chronicles?</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/dark-cowgirl-summoners-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/dark-cowgirl-summoners-war/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will explore the comparison between two popular damage dealers in the game Summoners War: Chronicles - CASSIE, the dark cowgirl, and KARAMBIT. These monsters have been a topic of discussion among players since the release of secret dungeons. We will delve into the damage output of both monsters and determine which one reigns supreme.
Testing Methodology
To compare the damage between CASSIE and KARAMBIT, I conducted a series of tests in the Naraka dungeon to mimic real-life scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> King&#39;s Raid Cain Review: The Ultimate Main DPS</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-cain-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-cain-review/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will be showcasing and providing a breakdown of the main DPS capabilities of Cain in the popular mobile game King&amp;rsquo;s Raid. Cain is a powerful character with unique skills and abilities that make him a formidable force in both PvP and PvE gameplay. We will delve into his kit, his scaling potential, and demonstrate his boss killing capabilities. So, let&amp;rsquo;s not waste any more time and dive right into the details!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Labyrinth Raid Beginner Guide: A Comprehensive Epic Seven Raid Guide for Royal Capital Azmakalis &#43; Cycle</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-raid-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Aug 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-raid-guide/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to our Epic Seven Labyrinth Raid Beginner Guide! In this guide, we will cover everything you need to know about the Royal Capital Azmakalis raid, including the basic rules, boss rewards, boss guides, recommended party compositions, and the shops. This raid has recently undergone significant changes, so it&amp;rsquo;s important to stay up-to-date.
Before we dive into the details, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to familiarize ourselves with some key points. The Royal Capital Azmakalis raid is now a one-time clear instead of a weekly reset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Make Your Shields Unbreakable: A Comprehensive Guide to Shield Buffs in Raid: Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-do-shields-stack/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-do-shields-stack/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will take a deep dive into Shield sets in Raid: Shadow Legends. Shields are an important aspect of the game that grant bonus HP or effective HP to your Champion, providing an extra layer of protection against incoming damage. However, not many players fully understand the intricacies of Shield sets and how they can be maximized for optimal gameplay. We will also discuss the new Bolster set and its potential impact in the top Arena meta.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Idle Heroes Tavern Quests - Guaranteed 7* Quest</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/idle-heroes-tavern-quests/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/idle-heroes-tavern-quests/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will be discussing a strategy to guarantee a 7-star quest in the popular mobile game, Idle Heroes. For those unfamiliar with the game, Idle Heroes is a role-playing game where players summon heroes, build a powerful team, and battle against various enemies. One of the key aspects of the game is completing quests, which can provide rewards and help progress the player&amp;rsquo;s account.
The Shadow Meme Team The transcript starts with the narrator, Barrygaming, discussing the &amp;ldquo;Shadow Meme Team&amp;rdquo; account that he hasn&amp;rsquo;t touched in a while.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Fragments of the Past: A Glimpse into an Imaginary World</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/crystal-restore-fragments-of-the-past/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/crystal-restore-fragments-of-the-past/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever found yourself captivated by the mysteries of ancient civilizations? The remnants of past cultures that have vanished over time can be incredibly intriguing, leaving us wondering about the untold stories and lost greatness of these civilizations. In the world of fantasy, the concept of exploring the fragments of the past takes shape, creating an immersive experience that echoes classical history and sparks our collective imagination.
&amp;ldquo;Fragments of the Past&amp;rdquo; is a fantasy world that breathes life into the artifacts and fragmented tales of ancient civilizations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars | The Best Heroes for Peppy Teams</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/peppy-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/peppy-teams/</guid>
      <description>In the realm of Dominion, the heroes are on a constant quest for power and victory. And when it comes to assembling a team, one hero stands out - Peppy. In this article, we will explore the best heroes to level up for Peppy teams and how they can optimize their skills for ultimate success. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and unlock the true potential of these peppy teams!
The Power of Collaboration: Cleaver and Peppy Peppy&amp;rsquo;s greatest strength lies in his collaboration with Cleaver.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kai vs. the Meta: Exploring Team Combinations in Hero Wars</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-kai/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-kai/</guid>
      <description>Unleash the Power of Kai Without K&amp;rsquo;arkh!
If you&amp;rsquo;re a fan of Hero Wars and have been following the recent updates, you know that Kai has undergone a rework on both the Facebook web and mobile platforms. In today&amp;rsquo;s video, we will delve into the world of Kai teams without the use of K&amp;rsquo;arkh. As we explore different team combinations, we will assess the effectiveness of Kai in the current meta and determine if he can hold his own against the top defending teams.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shop Titans Best Hero Guide: Tips &amp; Tricks for Building the Perfect Team</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/shop-heroes-team-builder/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/shop-heroes-team-builder/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to build a strong team of heroes in Shop Titans? Do you find the complexities of hero types, classes, elements, and team compositions overwhelming? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered! In this comprehensive guide, we will provide you with valuable tips and tricks to create the perfect team of heroes in Shop Titans. From understanding elemental barriers to choosing the right gear and skills, we&amp;rsquo;ve got all the information you need to level up your hero strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Evolution System in Summoners War has Changed, but Give it a Chance!</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-monsters-evolution/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-monsters-evolution/</guid>
      <description>Summoners War, an immensely popular mobile game, has recently made significant changes to its power up and evolution system. While some players may be feeling panicked and apprehensive about these changes, it is important to understand that the new system is actually an improvement in the long run. In this article, we will walk you through the new system and explain its structure, addressing any concerns you may have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Get Rich in Epic Seven - Best Place to Farm: Unrecorded History vs Hunt 13</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-hunt-farming/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-hunt-farming/</guid>
      <description>If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to amass a fortune in the popular mobile game Epic Seven, then this guide is for you. In this article, we will compare the benefits of farming in the Unrecorded History mode versus Hunt 13 during a buff event, helping you make an informed decision based on your needs. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re aiming to accumulate gold quickly or searching for specific loot, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered.
Understanding the Basics Before we dive into the details, let&amp;rsquo;s establish some key information.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars Mobile: Orion, Dorian &amp; Helios - The ODH Meta</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-orion-helios/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-orion-helios/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the exciting world of Hero Wars, there is a powerful combination of heroes that has taken the game by storm. Orion, Dorian, and Helios, also known as the Bloody Mary, have become a popular choice for players looking to counter crit teams. In this article, we will explore the mechanics behind this powerful team, the key role played by Helios, and the strategies to beat them.
The Power of Helios and Flaming Retribution The key to the Orion, Dorian, and Helios (ODH) meta lies in Helios&amp;rsquo; skill called Flaming Retribution.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ring of Darkness: The Superior Alternative to Band of Air?</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ring-of-darkness-game/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ring-of-darkness-game/</guid>
      <description>In the world of Neverwinter, changes are coming to the beloved Band of Air. Alongside this adjustment, the Ring of Darkness is also receiving some updates. In a recent blog post, Kobetic Studios explained the reasons behind these nerfs and adjustments, as well as their approach to balancing items in the game. This article will delve into the details of these changes and explore whether the Ring of Darkness has now surpassed the Band of Air in terms of potency.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Skill Builds, Relics, and Pets Guide: A Legendary Master Idle Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/idle-dps-legendary-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 29 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/idle-dps-legendary-guide/</guid>
      <description>Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced player, progressing in the game Legendary Master Idle can be challenging. In this guide, we will dive into the mechanics of Relics and skill builds to help you optimize your gameplay and make the most out of the resources you have. We&amp;rsquo;ll focus on a free-to-play friendly approach, so you don&amp;rsquo;t have to worry about spending real money to excel in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EVERY RARE CHAMP WORTH 6 STARS in 2023! | RAID Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-top-rare-champions/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-top-rare-champions/</guid>
      <description>By ASH: RAID Shadow Legends
Welcome to the world of RAID: Shadow Legends! In this video, we will discuss the top rare champions that are worth upgrading to 6 stars in the year 2023. While beauty is subjective, and you may have your own preferences, we will focus on champions that offer great utility and effectiveness in the game.
Before we dive into the recommended champions, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that rare champions can provide significant value, even at level 50.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Figure Out Combat Readiness (CR) in Epic Seven</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-figure-out-cr-in-epic-seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-figure-out-cr-in-epic-seven/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be delving into the intricacies of combat readiness (CR) and speed in Epic Seven. Many players struggle to understand these stats, but they are crucial for success, especially in PvP battles. We will explore the mechanics of speed and combat readiness, as well as provide tips on how to optimize these stats to gain an advantage in battles. Let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and unravel the mystery of combat readiness in Epic Seven!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Power of Shimitae (Wind Sylph) in RTA Special League Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summonerswar.co-wind-sylph/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 28 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summonerswar.co-wind-sylph/</guid>
      <description>In the world of Summoners War, one monster stands out as a force to be reckoned with in the Real-Time Arena Special League: Shimitae, the Wind Sylph. This powerful monster possesses abilities and skills that make it an invaluable asset in battles, both for beginners and experienced players. In this article, we will delve into the details of Shimitae&amp;rsquo;s abilities, its potential in RTA Special League, and how it can be a game-changer in your Summoners War journey.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Shadowshard vs. Obsidian: Making the Right Choice for Your Evolved Weapons</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/shadowshard-weapon/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/shadowshard-weapon/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will explore the question of whether you should evolve your weapons to shadowshard or obsidian in the popular game Fortnite: Save the World. This decision, which arises when evolving from a three to four-star weapon, can have a significant impact on your gameplay experience. We will discuss the differences between shadowshard and obsidian, as well as the pros and cons of each option.
Before we delve into the details, let&amp;rsquo;s take a moment to understand the evolution process in Fortnite: Save the World.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Labyrinth Raid Beginner Guide: Conquer the Royal Capital Azmakalis in Epic Seven!**</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-labyrinth-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-labyrinth-guide/</guid>
      <description>Are you ready to take on the challenges of the Royal Capital Azmakalis in Epic Seven? In this beginner guide, we will cover everything you need to know about this recently revamped raid. From the basic rules to boss strategies and recommended party compositions, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and conquer the labyrinth!
The Revamped Royal Capital Azmakalis
The Royal Capital Azmakalis, previously known as &amp;ldquo;normal raid,&amp;rdquo; has undergone significant changes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Beginner Guide: Start with These Commanders to Dominate in Rise of Kingdoms</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rok-commanders-recommended-for-beginners/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rok-commanders-recommended-for-beginners/</guid>
      <description>Are you a beginner in Rise of Kingdoms and looking for a guide on which commanders to focus on first? Look no further because in this article, we will discuss the very first commanders you should invest in to build up your power in the game. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a low spender or a no spender, these recommendations will help you make the most out of your gameplay. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in and explore the three categories of commanders you should prioritize as a new player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> HERO SKILLS REVEALED! An In-Depth Look at Kings Raid - Artemia, Mediana, and Theo!</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-heroes-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-heroes-skills/</guid>
      <description>In the ever-expanding world of Kings Raid, new heroes are constantly being introduced, each with their own unique set of skills and abilities. The latest heroes to be leaked are Artemia, Mediana, and Theo. In this article, we will take an in-depth look at their skills and discuss their potential in the game.
Artemia: The Pillar of Light Artemia is a powerful damage dealer with her arsenal of magical skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Unlock Alt. Ultimate Arena Pad and Clear Alt. Arena 3</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-unlock-alt.-ultimate-arena-pad/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-unlock-alt.-ultimate-arena-pad/</guid>
      <description>Alt. Arena 3 is a challenging dungeon in the popular mobile game, Puzzle &amp;amp; Dragons. In this article, we will guide you on how to unlock and clear Alt. Arena 3 using the powerful combination of Alice and Fasca. This strategy requires careful planning and execution, as well as a deep understanding of the game mechanics.
Step 1: Unlocking Alt. Ultimate Arena Pad To unlock Alt. Ultimate Arena Pad, you will need to complete certain requirements:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Trulight Selfie Flash: Red Light Therapy Explained and Best Devices for Any Budget</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/trulight-selfie-flash/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 26 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/trulight-selfie-flash/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to a deep dive into the realm of red light therapy. In this article, we will explore the science behind red light therapy, its benefits, and the best devices available on the market for any budget. Red light therapy has gained popularity as an effective and affordable way to promote health and well-being. So, let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
The Science Behind Red Light Therapy Before we delve into the benefits of red light therapy, it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand the science behind it.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hogwarts Legacy: Crafting Magical Soundscapes for the Wizarding World</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hogwarts-environs/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hogwarts-environs/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the realm of video game development, few projects can match the excitement and dedication that has gone into the creation of Hogwarts Legacy. As a member of the Avalanche sound team, I am fortunate enough to have spent the past four years working on this extraordinary endeavor. Among all the projects I&amp;rsquo;ve been involved in, Hogwarts Legacy truly stands as the pinnacle, taking the best elements of the Harry Potter films and adding a touch of new magic.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pro Ishmael Team Build as a Backline Hitter | Hero Wars Mobile</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-ishmael-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-ishmael-team/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome, Hero Wars players! Today, we will be discussing how to build a strong Ishmael team that excels at hitting the opponent&amp;rsquo;s backline. By utilizing Ishmael&amp;rsquo;s unique abilities, we can maximize his damage output and penetrate the enemy team&amp;rsquo;s armor. This team build is not only effective but also strategic, as it allows you to take down key targets quickly. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the details and explore the heroes that complement Ishmael in this build.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Importance of Dark Healers in Summoners War: The Real Reason for the Dark Vampire Lord</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-vampire-lord/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-vampire-lord/</guid>
      <description>In the world of Summoners War, a popular mobile game developed by Com2uS, players are constantly faced with new challenges and content updates. One such update introduced the Dark Vampire Lord, a highly anticipated unit that left many players wondering about its role and purpose in the game. In this article, we will delve into the real reason behind the introduction of the Dark Vampire Lord and its significance as a dark healer.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Beginner Guide to Fear The Darkness - Marvel Strike Force</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/msf-fear-the-darkness-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/msf-fear-the-darkness-guide/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this guide, we will discuss Fear The Darkness, a mode in the popular mobile game Marvel Strike Force. Fear The Darkness is a challenging mode that players must complete in order to unlock the powerful character Ultron. We will go over the basics of Fear The Darkness, how to unlock Ultron, and provide tips and strategies for success in this mode.
Understanding Fear The Darkness
Fear The Darkness is a game mode in Marvel Strike Force that players must complete in order to unlock the powerful character Ultron.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Blitz Guide Marvel Strike Force 2023: Maximizing Your Wins and Rewards</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-strike-force-blitz-team-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-strike-force-blitz-team-guide/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss how to effectively use the Blitz game mode in Marvel Strike Force to maximize your wins and rewards. Blitz offers players the opportunity to earn valuable resources and rewards by participating in battles and achieving milestones. We will cover the basics of Blitz, the importance of setting up your saved teams, and provide tips on how to strategically choose your opponents for maximum success.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sigmarus (Water Phoenix) - The Ultimate Guide for Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-rune-sigmarus-gb10/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-rune-sigmarus-gb10/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to SW Database, the most organized resource and the best place to learn about monsters in Summoners War. In this comprehensive guide, we will delve into everything you need to know about Sigmarus, the Water Phoenix. From where to use her and understanding her skills, to fusing her and the best runes for her, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover it all. Sigmarus is an exceptional monster for early to mid-game players and is highly versatile, making her a top-tier unit.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ultimate Field Fighting Guide: Master the Art of Open Field Combat in Rise of Kingdoms</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-attack-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 24 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-attack-guide/</guid>
      <description>In this comprehensive guide, we will take your Rise of Kingdoms gameplay to the next level by focusing on open field fighting. Whether you are a seasoned player with a stacked roster or a beginner entering your first KvK, the concepts presented in this guide will dramatically level up your skills in the open field. By mastering these strategies, you will be able to save resources and speed ups, secure wins, and achieve victory in Rise of Kingdoms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> All Rhinoceros Beetle Locations in Resident Evil 4: A Guide to Finding and Selling Rare Treasures</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/selling-rhinoceros-beetle/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/selling-rhinoceros-beetle/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the popular video game Resident Evil 4, players have the opportunity to collect rare treasures called Rhinoceros Beetles. These valuable items can be sold to the in-game merchant for a whopping 10,000 gold each. However, with the Rhinoceros Beetle charm equipped, players can sell each beetle for a staggering 20,000 gold, leading to a potential total of 60,000 gold. Additionally, consuming each beetle grants a permanent boost to the player&amp;rsquo;s health, similar to consuming a yellow herb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Best Crusader Build in Diablo Immortal: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/crusader-legendary-weapons/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/crusader-legendary-weapons/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this video transcript, we will discuss the best build for the Crusader class in Diablo Immortal. As an expert copywriter and experienced player, I will provide you with detailed information on the Crusader class, its strengths, the current build, and recommended legendary weapons to optimize your gameplay experience. Whether you are a new player or returning to the game, this guide will offer you a baseline build for the Crusader, along with additional options for different situations.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dumpster Diving: Uncovering Hidden Treasures in the Trash</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/trash-treasure-for-searching-ruins-table-rpg/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/trash-treasure-for-searching-ruins-table-rpg/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a common belief that one person&amp;rsquo;s trash is another person&amp;rsquo;s treasure. And in the realm of dumpster diving, this idea holds true. Many brave adventurers embark on the quest to find hidden gems amidst piles of discarded items. In this article, we will explore the thrilling world of dumpster diving and the unlikely treasures that can be found. Get ready to join Mike The Scavenger on an adventure as he uncovers a wide array of items from Amazon packages to pet sweaters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> WHAT ARTIFACTS TO SELL?? - A Comprehensive Guide for Epic Seven Players</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-farm-dust/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-farm-dust/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome back to another Epic Seven video guide! In today&amp;rsquo;s guide, we will be discussing the artifacts that you can safely sell for Powder of Knowledge. As the game introduces more limited and collaboration artifacts, it&amp;rsquo;s important to have enough Powder of Knowledge to purchase these valuable items. By selling artifacts that are not essential to your gameplay, you can accumulate more Powder of Knowledge. In this guide, I will provide you with a list of artifacts that you can safely sell, as well as those that you should keep for their usefulness in either PvE or PvP battles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Empires and Puzzles: Advanced Food Storage for Hero Academy Level 10</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-puzzles-advanced-food-storage/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-puzzles-advanced-food-storage/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the popular mobile game Empires and Puzzles, reaching Hero Academy Level 10 is a significant milestone. Once you have upgraded your academy, the next step is to focus on maximizing your food storages. This article will guide you through the process of storing iron, researching tiers, and upgrading your food storage efficiently. By following these steps, you&amp;rsquo;ll be able to make the most out of your resources and progress further in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars Satori Teams and Fight Compilation - Best Teams 2021</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-satori/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-satori/</guid>
      <description>Are you a Hero Wars player looking to optimize your gameplay with the powerful hero Satori? In this article, we will provide you with a compilation of some of the best Satori attacking lineups at the highest level of play. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re just starting to build Satori or want to learn how to use him effectively, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered. Get ready to gain some new inspiration and strategies for your future fights!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Labyrinth Raid Beginner Guide: Mastering Royal Capital Azmakalis and Cycle in Epic Seven</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-7-raid-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-7-raid-guide/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide for the Labyrinth Raid in Epic Seven! In this guide, we will cover everything you need to know about Royal Capital Azmakalis and the Astma Callus of Cycle in the Labyrinth Raid. This raid has recently undergone a major revamp, so it&amp;rsquo;s important to stay up-to-date with the changes. We will discuss the basic rules, boss rewards, boss strategies, recommended party compositions, and the shops in the raid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Top 10 Best Low Gear, Non-Legendary Teams for Free-To-Play Players 2023 in Star Wars Galaxy of Heroes</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/swgoh-top-100-squad-arena/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/swgoh-top-100-squad-arena/</guid>
      <description>In the world of Star Wars Galaxy of Heroes, being a successful player requires knowledge, strategy, and the ability to maximize your resources. As a free-to-play player, you have to make every credit and gear count, and that&amp;rsquo;s exactly what this article aims to help you with. We will be discussing the top 10 best low gear, non-legendary teams for free-to-play players in 2023.
But before we dive into the list, let&amp;rsquo;s establish some criteria.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> All 130 Golden Walnuts: A Comprehensive Stardew Valley Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/flowers-with-golden-seed/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/flowers-with-golden-seed/</guid>
      <description>Stardew Valley version 1.5 introduced a new and valuable currency known as Golden Walnuts. These walnuts are essential for exploring Ginger Island, and this guide will provide you with a step-by-step process to find all 130 of them. As you follow along, you&amp;rsquo;ll notice a little note in the top left of the screen that acts as a hint to locate each golden walnut. These hints are obtained by talking to the parrot in Leo&amp;rsquo;s height.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Beginner ISO Guide 2023: How to Farm ISO in Marvel Contest of Champions</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-champions-farm-iso/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-champions-farm-iso/</guid>
      <description>By Chewboom
Are you struggling to collect enough ISO in Marvel Contest of Champions? As a beginner player, it can be challenging to level up your champions without enough ISO. In this guide, I will provide you with the best strategies and tips on how to farm ISO efficiently. From completing quests to participating in events and utilizing the different in-game features, this guide will cover it all. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and level up your champions!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Beginner&#39;s Guide to King&#39;s Road: Tips and Strategy - Episode 1</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/beginner-guide-kings-road/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/beginner-guide-kings-road/</guid>
      <description>King&amp;rsquo;s Road is an exciting game that offers a thrilling gameplay experience. In this beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide, we will discuss various tips and strategies to help you navigate through the game more effectively. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a first-time player or looking to improve your skills, this article will provide you with valuable insights to succeed in King&amp;rsquo;s Road.
Understanding Weapons, Shields, and Armors One of the key aspects of King&amp;rsquo;s Road is the selection of weapons, shields, and armors.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ROK Rise of Kingdoms: The Fastest Fog Removal Strategy</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-scouting/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-scouting/</guid>
      <description>In the game Rise of Kingdoms, one of the quests players must complete is clearing the fog from their maps. This process can be time-consuming and tedious, but with the right strategy, it can be done quickly and efficiently. In this article, we will discuss the most efficient way to clear the fog from your maps in Rise of Kingdoms.
The Importance of Clearing the Fog Before diving into the strategy, let&amp;rsquo;s understand why clearing the fog is important in Rise of Kingdoms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Summoners War Rune Guide: How to Effectively Rune Lapis for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-rune-lapis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-rune-lapis/</guid>
      <description>Are you a beginner in Summoners War, struggling to understand how to effectively rune your Lapis? Look no further! In this comprehensive guide, we will walk you through everything you need to know about optimizing your Lapis with the best runes. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a new player or a seasoned summoner, this guide will help you make the most out of your Lapis and dominate in battles.
Why Runes Matter in Summoners War Before we dive into the specifics of rune selection for Lapis, let&amp;rsquo;s briefly discuss why runes are crucial in Summoners War.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Unlock the Power of Shop Refreshes: AFK Arena Store Guide [Furry Hippo Gaming]</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/afk-arena-store-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/afk-arena-store-guide/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will explore the importance of shop refreshes in AFK Arena and how they can help you in your gameplay. Shop refreshes provide you with the opportunity to acquire valuable items and resources that will enhance your heroes&amp;rsquo; abilities and progress in the game. Whether you are a new player or a seasoned veteran, this guide will help you understand the benefits of shop refreshes and how to make the most out of them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Grand Chase Classic Lime: Optimal Skill Tree for Maximum Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/grand-chase-lime-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/grand-chase-lime-build/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss the best skill tree for Lime in the popular game Grand Chase Classic. If you&amp;rsquo;re looking for tips to optimize your gameplay with Lime, you have come to the right place. We will break down each skill and provide detailed explanations to ensure you have a comprehensive understanding of how to build Lime for success.
Introduction Lime is a powerful character in Grand Chase Classic, known for her versatile skillset and high damage output.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> King&#39;s Raid - How to Build Tanks: A Comprehensive Guide to Tanking Strategies and Gear</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-block/</guid>
      <description>In the world of King&amp;rsquo;s Raid, one of the most important roles in any team is the tank. Tanks are crucial in providing protection to the team, mitigating damage, and ensuring the survival of the team in battles against bosses and monsters. However, choosing the right tank and gearing them properly can be a daunting task. In this guide, we will explore everything you need to know about tanks, from picking the right tank to optimizing their gear for maximum effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Mage PvE Class Guide: Everything You Need to Know About Ulala Mage Skills</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ulala-mage-skills/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ulala-mage-skills/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the mage class in Ulala Idle Adventure, a popular mobile game. The mage class, also known as the &amp;ldquo;meme master,&amp;rdquo; is a powerful and versatile class that excels in dealing damage, stunning enemies, and providing utility to the team. Whether you are new to the mage class or want to optimize your build for PvE content, this guide has got you covered.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ode To Heroes - Building Your First E5 Hero: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ode-to-heroes-good-4-star/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 20 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ode-to-heroes-good-4-star/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss the top picks for heroes that you should consider building as your first E5 hero in the popular game Ode To Heroes. We will go through each of the four factions and highlight the heroes that excel in the reincarnation trial, an important aspect of the game. We will also provide insights into their abilities and roles within the game.
Water Faction Lee Shishi: Lee Shishi is a support hero with high healing abilities and valuable buffs for her team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **Windwalker Monk Guide 10.1.5 WoW PvP Arena - Mastering the Powerful Talents**</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/monk-pvp-talents/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/monk-pvp-talents/</guid>
      <description>In this comprehensive guide, we will delve into the world of Windwalker Monks in World of Warcraft (WoW). We will explore the various talents, races, stats, gear, rotation, and compositions that can maximize your effectiveness as a Windwalker Monk in PvP arenas. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced player, this guide will provide you with valuable insights and strategies to dominate the PvP battlefield.
Talents: Unveiling the Optimal Choices When it comes to talents, the Windwalker Monk has a solid foundation that remains unchanged in the latest 10.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Top 10 Heroes to Limit Break in Green Empires and Puzzles: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-green-enemies/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-green-enemies/</guid>
      <description>In the world of Empires and Puzzles, choosing the right heroes to limit break can make a significant difference in your gameplay. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned player or just starting out, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to understand which heroes are worth investing in. In this guide, we will discuss the top 10 heroes to limit break in the green category. We will cover both five-star and lower star heroes, providing you with a comprehensive overview of their strengths and weaknesses.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>1 Arena Strategy to Max Towers Fast and Efficiently</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoner-wars-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 19 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoner-wars-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Summoner&amp;rsquo;s War is a popular mobile strategy game that involves battling and summoning creatures to fight for you. In the game, one important aspect to focus on is farming Glory Points from the Arena. Maxing out your Towers is crucial, and in this article, we will discuss a proven strategy to maximize your Towers quickly and efficiently.
The Importance of Maxing Towers
Maxing out your Towers in Summoner&amp;rsquo;s War is essential for several reasons.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 5 Unknown Tips for Winning Offensive Raids in Empires and Puzzles 2019</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-best-raid-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-best-raid-teams/</guid>
      <description>In this informative video, Anchor 7dd, the leader of Seven Days Departed, shares some lesser-known tips for winning offensive raids in the popular mobile game Empires and Puzzles. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or a seasoned player, these tips will help you improve your raiding skills and increase your chances of success.
Building the Correct Team
One of the first things to consider when building your raid team is your play style.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Best Builds for Tap Titans 2: Ultimate Guide for Version 5.10</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/tap-titans-2-pet-build-current/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/tap-titans-2-pet-build-current/</guid>
      <description>Tap Titans 2, one of the most popular mobile games, recently released its 5.10 update, which brought several changes to the skill system and the overall gameplay. With all these changes, players are left wondering which build is the best for their playstyle. In this article, we will explore the different builds available in Tap Titans 2 version 5.10 and provide you with the ultimate guide to help you choose the best build for your playstyle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars Secrets: Unleash the Power of JHU to Dominate the Game</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/jhu-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 18 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/jhu-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss the secrets of one of the most powerful heroes in Hero Wars, JHU. JHU is the 27th hero in the game, and we will explore which heroes he is strong against and how to build a team around him. We will also delve into his skills, strategies against bosses, and how to maximize his potential. Additionally, we will showcase battles with endgame heroes and pets to demonstrate JHU&amp;rsquo;s capabilities.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> AE Power Leveling: Is It The Right Way To Play City of Heroes?</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/city-of-heroes-leveling-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/city-of-heroes-leveling-guide/</guid>
      <description>In the City of Heroes community, power leveling via AE (Architect Entertainment) has become a controversial topic. AE allows players to access player-made missions, which can be a great addition to the game. However, many players openly criticize power leveling and farming in these missions. The question we are addressing in this article is whether or not power leveling in AE missions is the wrong way to play City of Heroes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Dreams Beneath the Searing Sand - Golden Slumber: A Guide to Completing the World Quests in Genshin Impact</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/genshin-pass-the-three-trials/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 16 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/genshin-pass-the-three-trials/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome back to our channel! In this video, we will be exploring the next part of the Golden Slumber questline in Genshin Impact. Specifically, we will be focusing on the Dreams Beneath the Searing Sand quest. As you progress through the previous quests, this one will automatically trigger. Join us as we navigate through this captivating world and uncover the secrets of the Searing Sand.
Step 1: Returning to the Oasis To begin this quest, your first task is to return to the Oasis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven Abyss Challenge Mode: Floor 1 - Purrgis - F2P Build - Easy Clear</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-7-what-is-the-abyss/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 15 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-7-what-is-the-abyss/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing the first floor of the Abyss Challenge Mode in the popular mobile game Epic Seven. Specifically, we will be focusing on strategies for defeating Purrgis, a formidable boss character. This guide is aimed at free-to-play players who may not have access to high-end gear or powerful units. We will provide step-by-step instructions on building a team and executing a successful clear of this floor.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars Mobile: Mastering the Low Cornelius Trick for Victory</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-cornelius/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-cornelius/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the Hero Wars Channel, where we uncover awesome tricks and strategies to dominate in the popular mobile game, Hero Wars. In this episode, we will explore a unique trick involving the low hero, Cornelius. By utilizing this technique, you can secure a win even against formidable enemies, especially those who have Unvari in their team. This trick involves using the Stone Grass ability to generate a significant amount of energy and strategically timing Cornelius&amp;rsquo; attack for maximum impact.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Kings Road Tips and Strategy: Episode 1</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/basic-kings-road-strategy/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/basic-kings-road-strategy/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Welcome, everyone, to this episode of Kings Road tips and strategy! In this series, we will be exploring the world of Kingdom gameplay and discussing various aspects of the game. In this first episode, we will be focusing on weapons, shields, and armor, and when to switch them out for optimal performance. So let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in!
Choosing the Right Weapons and Armor
When it comes to dual-wielding, it is crucial to wait until you obtain a more powerful sword than the one you currently have.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Prestige and Farming Guide 2021 for Tap Titans 2</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/tap-titans-2-artifacts-farming/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/tap-titans-2-artifacts-farming/</guid>
      <description>Tap Titans 2 is an exciting game that offers players the opportunity to progress through various stages and defeat powerful bosses. In order to maximize your gameplay experience and make significant progress, it is important to understand the concepts of prestige and farming. This guide will provide you with step-by-step instructions on how to effectively prestige and farm in Tap Titans 2, ensuring that you can become a master of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> A Comprehensive Guide to HHH Dungeon &amp; Crafting Level 50 Equipment in Ragnarok Origin</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/crystal-fragment-ragnarok/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/crystal-fragment-ragnarok/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: In this article, we will provide you with a detailed guide on how to navigate the HHH Dungeon and craft level 50 equipment in the popular game Ragnarok Origin. We will explain the different abbreviations used in the game, the process of obtaining blueprints, crafting equipment, and the importance of converters and accessories. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
Section 1: Understanding Abbreviations and Navigating the HHH Dungeon Abbreviations play a significant role in Ragnarok Origin, and understanding them is key to progressing in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Get Unlimited Gems in Empires and Puzzles (Android &amp; iOS) - A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-what-to-use-gems-for/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-what-to-use-gems-for/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Are you tired of constantly running out of gems in the popular game, Empires and Puzzles? Well, worry no more! In this article, we will show you a simple method to get unlimited gems in the game, without the need to download any files. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re playing on an Android or iOS device, this method will work seamlessly. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and find out how to unlock unlimited gems fast!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Top 5 Things You MUST Know About Outland in Hero Wars Facebook Version</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-outland-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 13 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-outland-wars/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will dive deep into the game activity called Outland on the Facebook version of Hero Wars. Outland is a significant feature in the game that becomes available to players once they reach Team level 25. It involves battling three bosses - Brog, Alyssa, and Vajar - to obtain valuable resources like skin stones. In this article, we will discuss everything you need to know about Outland, including the bosses, chests, and the Outland shop.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Doma Castle Dungeon Guide - Level 67 Dungeon in Final Fantasy XIV Stormblood</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ffxiv-doma-castle-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 12 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ffxiv-doma-castle-guide/</guid>
      <description>Note: This article is a transcription of a Youtube video guide by MTQcapture. It provides a detailed walkthrough of the Doma Castle dungeon in Final Fantasy XIV: Stormblood. The guide explains the mechanics of each boss encounter and provides tips on how to successfully navigate through the dungeon. Read on to learn how to conquer Doma Castle and emerge victorious!
Introduction Welcome to the visual guide for Doma Castle, a level 67 dungeon available in Final Fantasy XIV: Stormblood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> King&#39;s Raid: How to Obtain Heroes - A Comprehensive Starter&#39;s Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-how-to-get-heroes/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-how-to-get-heroes/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the ultimate guide on how to obtain heroes in the popular game King&amp;rsquo;s Raid. If you&amp;rsquo;re new to the game or coming from other similar games, you might be wondering how to summon heroes and build your team. In this article, we will discuss the different ways to get heroes and provide you with valuable tips and tricks to start your King&amp;rsquo;s Raid journey on the right foot.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sanctuary &#43; Breath of Orbis - How and Where to Use?? - What to Upgrade? - Epic Seven Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-spend-breath-of-orbis/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-spend-breath-of-orbis/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this guide, we will be discussing the topic of the sanctuary in Epic Seven and where you should be using your Breath of Orbis. Breath of Orbis can be obtained by completing adventure stages with a chaos gate symbol on the map. These items are crucial for upgrading buildings in the sanctuary, which provide various benefits to players. We will go through each building and its effects, as well as prioritize which ones to upgrade.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Which Build is Better for Lyn in Summoners War? Soul Link vs Non-Soul Link</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/light-amazon-summoners-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/light-amazon-summoners-war/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll be discussing the light Amazon monster Lyn and comparing two different builds for her in the popular mobile game Summoners War. Lyn is a four-star monster that is often considered a top-tier unit for both PvE and PvP content. We will explore the pros and cons of using either a Soul Link build or a Non-Soul Link build for Lyn and evaluate which build is better in terms of damage output and overall effectiveness.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> King&#39;s Raid: How to Get More Heroes for Free - Guide to the Hero&#39;s Inn</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-get-more-heroes-in-kings-raid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 10 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-get-more-heroes-in-kings-raid/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In the world of King&amp;rsquo;s Raid, obtaining new heroes for free is a goal that all players strive to achieve. Luckily, there is a hidden gem called the Hero&amp;rsquo;s Inn that allows players to acquire heroes without spending a single Ruby. In this guide, we will explore the Hero&amp;rsquo;s Inn and discover the secrets behind recruiting heroes for free.
The Heroes Inn: A Gateway to Free Heroes
Located in Alvia, the Hero&amp;rsquo;s Inn is run by the innkeeper Juno.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **How to Reroll to Get Your Desired Character in Gacha Games: A Comprehensive Guide**</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/reroll-rail/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/reroll-rail/</guid>
      <description>Gacha games have gained immense popularity worldwide due to their unique gameplay and collectible character system. One of the most crucial aspects of these games is acquiring powerful and desirable characters, often referred to as &amp;ldquo;waifus&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;husbandos.&amp;rdquo; In this article, we will discuss the elaborate process of rerolling in gacha games in order to obtain your dream character.
Introduction In the world of gacha games, rerolling refers to the practice of creating new accounts or restarting progress to maximize chances of obtaining powerful or rare characters.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 18 Rare Champions for End Game Content in RAID Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-judge/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-judge/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss the top 18 rare champions that are highly viable for end game content in RAID Shadow Legends. These champions are especially valuable in areas such as the Doom Tower and secret rooms. Although some of these champions may have been featured in previous videos, this list focuses on rare champions that excel in end game content. Let&amp;rsquo;s delve deeper into each champion&amp;rsquo;s unique abilities and why they are considered top-tier options for players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven: How to Maximize Your Sanctuary and Boost Rewards</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-breath-of-orbis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-breath-of-orbis/</guid>
      <description>Are you an Epic Seven player looking to maximize your Sanctuary and boost your rewards? If so, you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place. In this article, we will guide you through each of the buildings in the Sanctuary and provide tips on how to make the most out of them. From the heart of orbis to the steel workshop, the alchemist steeple, high command, and the forest of souls, we will cover it all.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> There is no such thing as a family crest! Uncovering the Salazar Family&#39;s Coat of Arms</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/salazar-family-crest/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/salazar-family-crest/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Have you ever wondered if your family has a coat of arms? In this article, we will follow the journey of Kelly Kraft as she explores her family&amp;rsquo;s history and discovers the truth behind her grandfather&amp;rsquo;s claims of a prestigious lineage. Join us as we delve into the fascinating world of genealogy and heraldry to uncover the secrets of the Salazar family crest.
Step 1: Begin with the Family Tree Kelly Kraft started her quest for the family crest by providing us with her family tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven Guide: Sanctuary &#43; Breath of Orbis - How and Where to Use??</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-breath-of-orbis-upgrade-order/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-breath-of-orbis-upgrade-order/</guid>
      <description>Are you a newcomer to Epic Seven and wondering how to effectively use Breath of Orbis and upgrade your Sanctuary? In this guide, we will cover everything you need to know about utilizing this vital resource and optimizing your upgrades in the game. From the Heart of Orbis to the Steel Workshop, we will discuss the order in which you should prioritize your upgrades and how they will benefit you as a player.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Every Rare Champion Worth Upgrading to 6 Stars in 2023 in RAID Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/good-rare-champions-raid-shadow-legends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/good-rare-champions-raid-shadow-legends/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the world of RAID Shadow Legends! In this article, we will be discussing the rare champions that are definitely worth upgrading to 6 stars in the year 2023. With the vast collection of champions available in the game, it can be overwhelming to choose which ones to invest in. However, fear not! We have compiled a list of the top rare champions that will bring immense value to your team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Making a Block of Perfectly Clear Ice: A Step-by-Step Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/nile-club-red/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/nile-club-red/</guid>
      <description>Have you ever looked at a regular ice cube and thought it was just too dull and unappealing? Well, you&amp;rsquo;re not alone. In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore how to create a block of perfectly clear ice that is not only visually stunning but also enhances the overall drinking experience. Follow this step-by-step guide to achieve the perfect ice cube.
Step 1: Gather Your Materials To start this ice-making journey, you&amp;rsquo;ll need a few essential items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Nameless Thanos Final Boss Fight - Grandmasters Gauntlet 2021 - Marvel Contest of Champions</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/legendary-marvel-shards-on-bosses/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 08 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/legendary-marvel-shards-on-bosses/</guid>
      <description>In the thrilling conclusion of the Grandmasters Gauntlet 2021 event in Marvel Contest of Champions, players come face to face with the formidable Nameless Thanos. With a staggering 129k health pool, this final boss fight is not for the faint of heart. However, as our expert copywriter will show you, with the right strategies and champions, victory is within reach.
Introduction The Grandmasters Gauntlet event in Marvel Contest of Champions is a challenging quest that tests the skills and knowledge of even the most experienced players.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven: Enhancing Your Sanctuary for Maximum Efficiency and Rewards</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-heart-of-orbis/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-heart-of-orbis/</guid>
      <description>In the popular mobile game Epic Seven, the sanctuary plays a crucial role in providing players with valuable resources and rewards. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a free player or a paying one, knowing how to optimize your sanctuary is essential to maximizing your progress in the game. In this article, we will delve into the key buildings within the sanctuary and discuss how to make the most out of them.
Maximizing the Heart of Orbis One of the most important buildings in the sanctuary is the Heart of Orbis.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> WHICH RARES SHOULD YOU 6 STAR IN 2023? | Raid: Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-list-of-best-rares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 07 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-list-of-best-rares/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss which rare champions in Raid: Shadow Legends are worth 6 starring in 2023. This is a popular question among players, especially for those who are new to the game or aiming to tackle the end-game content, such as the Doom Tower hard secret rooms. We will provide a detailed analysis of each rare champion and their usefulness in different aspects of the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 3 Uncommon Champs in Raid Shadow Legends: A Guide to Building Them</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-crusader/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 06 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-crusader/</guid>
      <description>In this guide, we will be discussing three of the best uncommon champions in Raid Shadow Legends. These champions may not be legendary or epic, but they are definitely worth investing in and maximizing. We will cover where to use them and provide tips on how to build them effectively.
Before we dive into the details of these champions, let&amp;rsquo;s give a shout-out to some other uncommon champions that didn&amp;rsquo;t make the top three list.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars Mobile KSJ Keira Sebastian Jet Guide - Master the Meta Episode 001</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kiera-pvp-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kiera-pvp-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to the jungle! In this guide, we will explain the powerful and interesting combination of heroes: Kiera, Sebastian, and Jet. This team has proven to be extremely strong and effective, especially in guild wars and cross-server battles.
Unlock the True Power of Kiera Kiera is the backbone of this team, as her damage output is insane. Her first strike ability can deal devastating damage to enemy teams, making her a must-have in any PvP lineup.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Let&#39;s Play Hero Wars 45: Introducing Krista, the New Hero</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-krista/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 04 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-krista/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this episode of &amp;ldquo;Let&amp;rsquo;s Play Hero Wars,&amp;rdquo; we are introduced to the new hero, Krista. Join us as we explore her abilities, test her in battles, and see how she can be integrated into our teams. Krista is an exciting addition to the Hero Wars roster, and we can&amp;rsquo;t wait to see what she brings to the game.
Arena Battles We start off the video with some arena battles, aiming to quickly complete our fights before running out of time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 5 Important Tips for Emblems in Empires and Puzzles</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-best-wizard-talent-grid/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-best-wizard-talent-grid/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss the importance of emblems in the popular game of Empires and Puzzles. Emblems have become the most essential commodity in the game, surpassing heroes and other items in importance. By following these five important tips, players can make the most out of their emblems and excel in the game.
1. Collecting and Managing Emblems
Emblems are now the most important thing to collect in Empires and Puzzles.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Champion Review: A Complete Analysis of Swordsman in RAID: Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-swordsman/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-shadow-legends-swordsman/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
Welcome to another champion review by SprinkleBeard! In this article, we will be discussing Swordsman, a common magic champion in RAID: Shadow Legends. Swordsman is often obtained when opening mystery shards, so it&amp;rsquo;s important to understand his strengths and weaknesses. Before we dive into the details, be sure to check out our Twitch channel at twitch.tv/sprinklebeard, where we stream daily from 11 a.m. to 3 p.m. Eastern Standard Time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Empires and Puzzles Talent Grid Guide: How to Level a Hero the Right Way</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-talent-grid-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/empires-and-puzzles-talent-grid-guide/</guid>
      <description>In the world of Empires and Puzzles, leveling up your heroes is a crucial step towards building a formidable team. While there are various methods to level up your heroes, it&amp;rsquo;s important to know the proper way to ensure your heroes reach their highest potential. In this guide, we will walk you through the basics of leveling a hero, as well as provide some tips on how to efficiently level up their talent grid.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven Sanctuary Improvements: Maximizing Rewards and Efficiency</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/sanctuary-upgrade-epic-seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/sanctuary-upgrade-epic-seven/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will be discussing how to upgrade your sanctuary in the popular mobile game, Epic Seven. As a free player, it&amp;rsquo;s essential to know where to spend your points and how to make your sanctuary as efficient as possible. By maximizing your sanctuary, you can maximize your rewards and have more fun in the game. We will be discussing each building in detail and providing step-by-step instructions on how to make the most of each one.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ode to Heroes - A Comprehensive Guide to Choosing Your First E5 Hero</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ode-to-heroes-characters/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ode-to-heroes-characters/</guid>
      <description>Ode to Heroes is a popular mobile game that allows players to collect and build a team of powerful heroes. In this article, we will discuss the top picks for heroes that you should consider building as your first E5 hero, from each of the four factions: water, fire, wind, and earth. We will also analyze their abilities and strengths, with a focus on their performance in the reincarnation trial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Strong Hero Combos That Can Dominate Hero Wars Battles</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kai-and-thea-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 03 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kai-and-thea-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In Hero Wars, choosing the right heroes can make or break your chances of success. That&amp;rsquo;s why we have decided to highlight some powerful hero combinations that can increase your chances of winning battles and earning bigger rewards. In this article, we will discuss three great combos of heroes that have exceptional synergy and can turn the tide of any battle in your favor.
Combo 1: Larson and Christa - The Sibling Synergy The first deadly pair we will talk about is Larson and Christa, a brother and sister duo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven: A Comprehensive Guide to Sanctuary Improvements</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/breath-of-orbis-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/breath-of-orbis-guide/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to the ultimate guide for improving your sanctuary in Epic Seven. In this article, we will discuss the best strategies for maximizing your rewards, optimizing your buildings, and making the most out of your resources. Whether you are a free player or a seasoned veteran, these tips will help you enhance your gaming experience and thrive in the world of Epic Seven.
The Heart of Orbis The Heart of Orbis is the first building we will focus on.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Level-Up Special Abilities for Beginners in Marvel Strike Force</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-strike-force-best-level-7-abilities/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/marvel-strike-force-best-level-7-abilities/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will explore the world of special abilities in Marvel Strike Force and learn how to level them up to dominate your opponents. Special abilities are the actions and attacks that your characters can use in battle, and they become available as you train your character and raise their gear tier. By understanding how to effectively level-up these abilities, you can turn your heroes and villains into battle-winning superstars.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> X-HERO Free Diamonds: A Step-by-Step Guide to Getting Unlimited Diamonds with X-HERO Hack 2023</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/x-hero-exchange-code/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/x-hero-exchange-code/</guid>
      <description>In this comprehensive tutorial, we will show you how to obtain free unlimited diamonds in the popular game X-HERO. By utilizing the modded version of X-HERO called X hero plus plus, players can easily acquire a significant number of diamonds within seconds, without the need for root or jailbreak. This exclusive modded version is compatible with both Android and iOS devices, making it accessible to a wide range of gamers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Summoners: How to Get a 7-Star Hero Easily and Quickly</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-summoners-how-to-get-7-star-hero/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-summoners-how-to-get-7-star-hero/</guid>
      <description>Are you an Epic Summoners enthusiast looking to level up your gameplay? Do you want to know how to obtain a 7-Star Hero without any hassle? Look no further, as we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered! In this article, we will guide you step by step on how to acquire a 7-Star Hero in Epic Summoners, sharing tips and tricks and shedding light on the process.
Before we dive into the details, let&amp;rsquo;s talk about the requirements and strategies involved in obtaining a 7-Star Hero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Fire Magic Knight Astar: Unlocking the Power of Summoners War Chronicles</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/fire-magic-knight-sw/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/fire-magic-knight-sw/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to Summoners War Chronicles! In this article, we will discuss the exciting world of Fire Magic Knight Astar. Astar is a powerful monster that can greatly enhance your gameplay experience in Summoners War. We will explore how to obtain this monster, its unique abilities, and its potential as a member of your attack speed team. So sit back, relax, and let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the magical realm of Summoners War!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Summoners War | How to Optimize Lapis&#39; Runes for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-magic-knight-runes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-magic-knight-runes/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the vast and fantastical world of Summoners War, one of the key aspects of the game is building and optimizing your team of monsters. Lapis, the Water Magic Knight, is a popular choice for beginners due to her versatility and effectiveness in various game modes. However, to truly unleash her potential, it is crucial to equip her with the most suitable runes. In this article, we will guide you through an effective rune setup for Lapis and provide a beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide to maximize her performance.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> TOP 5 KILLER TANK HEROES IN MOBILE LEGENDS: A Guide to the Best Tanks in 2019</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/best-tank-in-mobile-legends-2019/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/best-tank-in-mobile-legends-2019/</guid>
      <description>Mobile Legends, a popular MOBA game developed by Moontoon, offers players a wide range of heroes to choose from. Among these heroes, tanks play a crucial role in protecting their teams and initiating team fights. In this article, we will discuss the top 5 killer tank heroes in Mobile Legends for the year 2019. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a seasoned player or a beginner, this guide will help you make an informed decision when choosing a tank hero.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Who Does Dorian Synergize Well With? The Ultimate Healer Guide | Hero Wars Mobile</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-how-to-use-dorian/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-how-to-use-dorian/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome back, Hero Wars players! In today&amp;rsquo;s article, we will be diving into the best possible ways to utilize the powerful hero, Dorian. By understanding the importance of Hero placement and synergy within a team, you will discover the incredible potential that Dorian brings to your strategies. So, let&amp;rsquo;s not waste any more time and get right into it!
Understanding Dorian&amp;rsquo;s Abilities Dorian, as a backline hero, offers a unique physical attack boost to the team through his artifact weapon.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> RS3: Rune Mechanics Quest Guide - Easy Steps to Complete the Quest</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rune-mechanics-quest/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rune-mechanics-quest/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the RuneScape world, the Rune Mechanics quest is an essential task that every player needs to complete. To ensure your success, this guide will provide you with easy step-by-step instructions on how to complete the quest. By following these instructions, you can quickly gather the required items and overcome any obstacles that may come your way.
Getting Started To begin the Rune Mechanics quest, you will need the following items:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ultimate Field Fighting Guide: Mastering Open Field Battles in Rise of Kingdoms</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-how-holy-places-pvp-mechanics/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-how-holy-places-pvp-mechanics/</guid>
      <description>Note: This video is a transcription of a YouTube video by Chisgule Gaming.
If you&amp;rsquo;re looking to level up your gameplay in Rise of Kingdoms and become a pro in open field fighting, regardless of your roster&amp;rsquo;s power or experience level, then you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place. In this ultimate guide, we will explore the concepts and strategies that will dramatically improve your skill in open field battles. This will not only save you valuable resources and speed-ups but also lead to victories in the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> WHICH RARES SHOULD YOU 6 STAR IN 2023? | Raid: Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-useful-rares/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/raid-useful-rares/</guid>
      <description>Raid: Shadow Legends is a popular gaming app that has gained a lot of attention and popularity in recent years. As a player progresses in the game, they often come across the question of which rare champions are useful and which ones are not. In this article, we will explore the different rare champions in the game and discuss which ones are worth investing in for future gameplay.
Before delving into the individual champions, it is important to note a few things.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> With Roblox ADMIN I created an Invisible Maze of Death</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/the-invisible-maze/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 30 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/the-invisible-maze/</guid>
      <description>Roblox is a popular online game platform where users can create and play games. In this video, we follow Flamingo as he uses his Roblox admin powers to create an invisible maze that kills the players.
Imagine having an electric fence in your yard to keep your dog from wandering off. Flamingo uses a similar concept to create a maze in Roblox. The maze is made up of invisible blocks that players have to navigate through.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Courier Station Shopping Tips in Rise of Kingdoms: What to Buy (And What to Avoid)</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-courier-station/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-courier-station/</guid>
      <description>When playing Rise of Kingdoms, one of the regular events that you will encounter is the Traveling Creator in your Courier Station. This event offers a variety of items for purchase, but it&amp;rsquo;s important to know which ones are worth buying and which ones you should avoid. In this article, we will provide you with valuable tips and insights on how to make the most out of your purchases in the Courier Station.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven Nightmare Raid - A Foolproof Guide to Defeating All Bosses</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-raid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-raid/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will be discussing the best strategies and teams to use in order to achieve a 100% clear rate in the Nightmare Raid in Epic Seven. This guide will provide you with step-by-step instructions on how to successfully defeat all bosses in the raid. We will also discuss alternative units and artifacts that can be used if you do not have the recommended ones. By following this guide, you will be able to make your monthly grind in the Nightmare Raid much easier and more efficient.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars: The Ultimate Guide to Obtaining All 30 Titan Totems</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-obtaining-totem/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-obtaining-totem/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the popular game Hero Wars, obtaining Titan Totems is an essential part of enhancing your gameplay and strengthening your team. These totems provide significant benefits and can greatly improve your chances of success in battles and guild wars. In this comprehensive guide, we will explore the guaranteed method for obtaining all 30 Titan Totems. We will discuss the changes made to the old charts and provide step-by-step instructions on how to maximize your chances of obtaining these valuable items.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Is Jet Worth it in Hero Wars? A Comparison with Fafnir 😲</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/is-jet-worth-it-in-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/is-jet-worth-it-in-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back to Eagle Eye Gaming, Hero Power Players! In today&amp;rsquo;s video, we will be discussing the need to build Jet in the current state of the game. We will also compare Jet with Fafnir, an alternative support character in Hero Wars Mobile. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in!
Before the release of Fafnir in the game, many players chose to build Jet for various reasons. Jet&amp;rsquo;s main advantage was his crit ability, which provided a chance for double physical damage to physical attackers, even if they didn&amp;rsquo;t have great abilities themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> SO MANY GOOD BANNERS! - A Guide on Summoning in Epic Seven</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-release-banners/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-release-banners/</guid>
      <description>Epic Seven is currently running a series of exciting banners and collaborations, leaving players wondering how to prioritize their limited resources. In this guide, we will discuss the best approach for new, mid, and late-game players when it comes to summoning. Whether you are a seasoned player or just starting out, we have you covered.
1. Skip Regular Banners: Despite the allure of regular banners, it is generally recommended to skip them.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic 7: The Struggle to Play - Overcoming Technical Challenges</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/achievements-epic-seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/achievements-epic-seven/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the world of mobile gaming, Epic 7 has gained popularity as an exciting and immersive role-playing game. However, many players have encountered numerous technical difficulties when trying to access and play the game. From infuriating captchas to invisible letters, the hurdles seem endless. In this article, we will delve into the challenges players face and explore possible solutions to overcome them.
The Captcha Challenge One of the major obstacles that players encounter is the challenging captcha system.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EPIC SEVEN Friendship Grind Guide: How to Farm Fodders, Friendship Points, and Levels</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-friendship-grind/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-friendship-grind/</guid>
      <description>Learn the Ultimate Strategy for Epic Seven Farming
In this guide, we will explore the best method for farming in Epic Seven, specifically focusing on how to farm forever, farm fodders, friendship points, friendship experience, and friendship levels. Additionally, we will uncover the ideal locations to obtain slime jelly and eternal forest dust, as well as the benefits of running this method. So, if you&amp;rsquo;re an Epic Seven player looking to maximize your farming potential, this guide is for you!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> EPIC SEVEN Maya Hero Review - Best Builds and Artifacts for a Good Artifact for Maya</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/good-artifact-for-maya-epic-seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/good-artifact-for-maya-epic-seven/</guid>
      <description>Maya is a 4-star hero in the popular mobile game EPIC SEVEN. In this guide, we will review Maya&amp;rsquo;s skills, analyze the best items and sets for her, and discuss the ideal artifact builds for this F2P hero. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a beginner or an experienced player, this article will provide you with all the information you need to maximize Maya&amp;rsquo;s potential in your lineup.
Maya&amp;rsquo;s Skills Review Before discussing Maya&amp;rsquo;s optimal builds, let&amp;rsquo;s take a closer look at her skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven Nightmare Raid - The Ultimate Guide to Clearing All Bosses</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-7-raid-team/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-7-raid-team/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to clear the Nightmare Asthma Callous raid in Epic Seven? Look no further. In this article, we will guide you through a step-by-step process to create your own 100% clear raid team. These teams are reliable, fast, and will make your monthly grind much easier. So, let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
Introduction Before we dive into the team compositions, let&amp;rsquo;s go over a few alternatives to the units mentioned in this guide.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> King&#39;s Raid - Mastering Wave Dodging in Trial of Flow: A Technique to Boost Your DPS</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-dodge/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-dodge/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling to clear stages nine and ten in King&amp;rsquo;s Raid&amp;rsquo;s Trial of Flow? Do you find that the boss has too much health and deals so much damage that it&amp;rsquo;s impossible to keep your DPS alive? Look no further! In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll explore a technique called wave dodging that can significantly boost your DPS and increase your chances of clearing these challenging stages.
The Problem with the Boss&amp;rsquo;s Skills The boss in Trial of Flow has skills that deal devastating damage to your DPS heroes, making it nearly impossible to keep them alive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Sanitarium: A Gripping iOS/Android Gameplay Experience</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/sanitarium-walkthrough-iphone/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/sanitarium-walkthrough-iphone/</guid>
      <description>Are you in search of a thrilling and immersive gameplay experience on your iOS or Android device? Look no further than Sanitarium, a game that will keep you on the edge of your seat. In this article, we will be exploring the captivating world of Sanitarium, discussing its intriguing storyline, mesmerizing graphics, and addictive gameplay. So buckle up and get ready for a wild ride!
The Mysterious World of Sanitarium In the dark and twisted universe of Sanitarium, you find yourself in a mental institution without any recollection of who you are or how you ended up there.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Summoners War | A Comprehensive Guide on Effectively Running Lapis - Best Beginner&#39;s Tips!</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summonerwar.co-lapis/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summonerwar.co-lapis/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the popular mobile game Summoners War, players are constantly seeking ways to improve their gameplay and enhance their strategies. One crucial aspect of the game is effectively running characters, and in this article, we will dive deep into how to efficiently rune one specific character - Lapis. Here, you will find step-by-step instructions and valuable tips to maximize Lapis&amp;rsquo; potential and elevate your gaming experience.
Understanding Lapis and its Importance Lapis is a powerful water-type monster in Summoners War, known for her versatile and adaptable skills.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Beginner Guide to Fear The Darkness - Marvel Strike Force - MSF</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/msf-fear-the-darkness/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/msf-fear-the-darkness/</guid>
      <description>Are you a Marvel Strike Force player looking to conquer the Fear The Darkness mode and unlock Ultron, the most powerful character in the game? Fear no more! In this comprehensive beginner&amp;rsquo;s guide, we will walk you through the intricacies of this challenging mode and provide you with all the tips and strategies you need to succeed.
But before we dive into the specifics, let&amp;rsquo;s address a pressing question: why do we have daylight savings time?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How Good is Galahad? A Comprehensive Analysis of Hero Wars&#39; Tank Hero</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-best-galahad-skin/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-best-galahad-skin/</guid>
      <description>When it comes to tank heroes in Hero Wars Mobile, Galahad often gets a bad reputation. In this article, we will dive into the strengths and weaknesses of Galahad and evaluate whether he deserves this criticism or not. We will also discuss potential strategies to maximize his effectiveness in your team.
Before we begin, let&amp;rsquo;s clarify that Galahad is considered one of the worst tank heroes in the game. However, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that this analysis is based on his role as a frontline hero designed to protect your team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Ode to Heroes - A Comprehensive Tier List and Guide for Beginners</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ode-to-heroes-tier-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 27 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/ode-to-heroes-tier-list/</guid>
      <description>Are you just starting out on your Ode to Heroes journey and feeling a bit overwhelmed? Don&amp;rsquo;t worry, we&amp;rsquo;ve got you covered! In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll provide you with a comprehensive tier list for both PvP and PvE, along with a detailed guide that has everything you need to know about the game. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a newbie or a seasoned player, this article will help you make the right choices and progress in Ode to Heroes effectively.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> All the Ways to Get Speedups in Rise of Kingdoms [F2P and Spending]</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-f2p-speed-boost/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/rise-of-kingdoms-f2p-speed-boost/</guid>
      <description>Welcome back, friends! Today, we are going to delve into the topic of getting more speedups in Rise of Kingdoms. Speedups are an essential resource in the game that can accelerate your progress and help you train troops faster. In this article, we will explore all the different ways you can obtain speedups in 2020. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive right in!
In-Game Stores The first category we will discuss is the in-game stores.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> King&#39;s Raid - PVE Team Test: Jane, Viska, Mirianne, Kaulah</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-viska-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-viska-build/</guid>
      <description>In this video, we will be showcasing a random team consisting of Jane, Viska, Mirianne, and Kaulah in various PVE areas of the game King&amp;rsquo;s Raid. We will be testing their performance in Adventure 7, Red Dragon 75, and Tower of Challenge 65. Let&amp;rsquo;s take a look at the stats and gear of each hero before we begin.
Jane:
Class: Warrior Stats: Standart angle with P block and unblock Gear: Ogre Viska:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Ultimate Guide to Genshin Impact: Avoid These Mistakes!</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/adventure-camp-genshin/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 26 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/adventure-camp-genshin/</guid>
      <description>Genshin Impact has taken the gaming world by storm, offering players an immersive open-world experience filled with adventure, exploration, and thrilling battles. But like any game, there are common mistakes that beginners and even experienced players can make.
In this article, we&amp;rsquo;ll discuss the top mistakes to avoid in Genshin Impact and how you can improve your gameplay to ensure a successful and enjoyable experience. So grab your weapons, gather your companions, and let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the world of Teyvat!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> **The Best Titan Brawl Team in Hero Wars Mobile: A Strategy Guide**</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-titan-teams/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-titan-teams/</guid>
      <description>Channel Name: Hero Wars Central
In this guide, we will discuss the Titan Brawl activity in Hero Wars mobile and the best team to use for optimal results. Before we dive into the strategy, let&amp;rsquo;s cover some important reminders. It&amp;rsquo;s crucial to set your defense every day to ensure your Titans are protecting your dominion. Additionally, it&amp;rsquo;s advisable to accumulate 240 tokens before engaging in Titan Brawl fights. Each fight costs 6 tokens and you don&amp;rsquo;t lose them if you lose a battle, but you will lose them if you win.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Become a GM in Hero Wars Ginger with the VIP Cheat</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-ginger-apk-mod/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-ginger-apk-mod/</guid>
      <description>Are you tired of playing Hero Wars Ginger and not being able to progress? Do you want to become a GM and have all the benefits that come with it? Well, look no further! In this article, we will show you how to become a GM in Hero Wars Ginger using a VIP cheat.
Hero Wars Ginger is a popular mobile game where players take on the role of a hero and battle their way through various levels and challenges.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Pokémon Masters Chapter 17: Battling A Ghostly Trio of Female Masters in the PML!!</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/pokemon-masters-chapter-17/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 25 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/pokemon-masters-chapter-17/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will be discussing Chapter 17 of Pokémon Masters, where we will be battling against a ghostly trio of female masters in the Pokémon Masters League (PML). This chapter introduces us to Sorella Phoebe, Acerola, and Agatha, who form a formidable team. We will dive into the details of this chapter, including the battle strategies, team dynamics, and the overall storyline. So, let&amp;rsquo;s get started!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven: How to Obtain and Utilize Breath of Orbis Effectively</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/orbis-locations-epic-seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/orbis-locations-epic-seven/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will explore the methods to obtain Breath of Orbis and how to effectively utilize this valuable resource in the popular mobile game, Epic Seven. Breath of Orbis serves as a crucial component in upgrading buildings within the game, and understanding its importance can greatly enhance your gameplay experience. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and discover the key points regarding Breath of Orbis.
Obtaining Breath of Orbis To obtain Breath of Orbis, follow these simple steps:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Summoners War Tips and Secrets: 20 Essential Tips for New Players</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-tips-and-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 24 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-tips-and-secrets/</guid>
      <description>Introduction If you&amp;rsquo;ve recently downloaded Summoners War and are just starting your journey, this article is for you. In this guide, we will provide you with 20 essential tips to help new players navigate the game and progress efficiently. From completing the Summoner&amp;rsquo;s Way questline to building an effective team, we&amp;rsquo;ll cover it all. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive in and discover the key strategies and secrets to success in Summoners War.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hell Raid Detailed Guide: Tackling the First Four Bosses - Epic Seven Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/good-raid-team-epic-seven/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/good-raid-team-epic-seven/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Welcome to another Epic Seven video! In today&amp;rsquo;s video, I will be providing a detailed guide on the Hell Raid and Normal Raid in Epic Seven. This guide will cover the units you should build for Hell Raid, as well as strategies for tackling each boss. Whether you&amp;rsquo;re a new player or looking to optimize your raid team, this guide will provide you with valuable insights and tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Hero Wars Secrets: Unleashing the Power of JHU</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-upgrade-jhu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-upgrade-jhu/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this article, we will delve into the secrets of Hero Wars&amp;rsquo; 27th hero, JHU. We will discuss JHU&amp;rsquo;s strengths, the heroes he excels against, and how to effectively build a team around him considering the ascension tree. Additionally, we will explore JHU&amp;rsquo;s skills, how to use him against bosses, and strategies for building him up. Get ready to unlock the full potential of JHU and dominate the game!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Build Nebula in Hero Wars: A Comprehensive Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-nebula/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/hero-wars-nebula/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In Hero Wars, the hero of the month for Facebook and web players is Nebula. Nebula is an essential hero to obtain and level up for various reasons, particularly for the guild raid fight against Osh in the Asgard Activity. In this article, we will explore why Nebula is important, discuss her skills and statistics, and provide insight into building her effectively.
The Significance of Nebula Nebula is a versatile hero that offers great value in both PvP and PvE scenarios.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Master Lars in Tekken 7: An In-Depth Guide</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/lars-guide/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/lars-guide/</guid>
      <description>Tekken 7 is a game known for its array of diverse characters, each with their own unique playstyles and strengths. One character that has gained attention is Lars, who, despite struggling initially, has become a strong contender with each passing season. In this guide, we will delve into the intricacies of playing and beating Lars, providing you with a comprehensive breakdown of his moves, strengths, weaknesses, and expert tips.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> King&#39;s Raid - How to Build Tanks: A Comprehensive Guide to Tanking in King&#39;s Raid</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-p.-block/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 23 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-p.-block/</guid>
      <description>Are you struggling with choosing the right tank for your team in King&amp;rsquo;s Raid? Do you want to know how to gear them up effectively? In this article, we will delve into the world of tanks in King&amp;rsquo;s Raid and provide you with all the information you need to become a master tank. Whether you are a beginner or an experienced player, this guide will help you make informed decisions when it comes to building tanks.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 5 Mistakes Beginners Make in Hero Wars: Dominion Era</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-remove-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/how-to-remove-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Hero Wars is an exciting game that attracts many beginners. However, there are common mistakes that new players often make that hinder their progress. In this article, we will discuss the top 5 mistakes beginners make in Hero Wars and provide valuable tips on how to avoid them. By following these tips, you can ensure a successful start to your Hero Wars journey.
1. Upgrading All Heroes Indiscriminately One of the most common mistakes beginners make in Hero Wars is upgrading all their heroes without a strategy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> ALL 2022 SWGOH NEW CHARACTERS AND SHIPS RANKED TIER LIST: A Comprehensive Review</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/galaxy-of-heroes-tier-list/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/galaxy-of-heroes-tier-list/</guid>
      <description>Introduction:
In this article, we will be discussing the new characters and ships that were introduced in 2022 in the popular mobile game Star Wars: Galaxy of Heroes (SWGOH). As a seasoned player, I have had the opportunity to evaluate and rank these new additions based on their performance and usefulness in the game. Whether you are a new player or a veteran, this article will provide you with insights into the strengths and weaknesses of these characters and ships.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Significance of the Dark Vampire Lord in Summoners War</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-dark-vampire-lord/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 22 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/summoners-war-dark-vampire-lord/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In the world of Summoners War, the recent addition of the Dark Vampire Lord has left many players wondering about its purpose and usefulness. In this article, we will delve into the real reason behind the introduction of this character and analyze its potential in the game. As an experienced player and former game developer, I believe there is a specific need that the Dark Vampire Lord fulfills within the game.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> 3 Effective Strategies to Counter Any Team in Hero Wars Mobile</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/heroes-that-counter-luther-hero-wars/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/heroes-that-counter-luther-hero-wars/</guid>
      <description>Whether you&amp;rsquo;re playing in an in-game battle or participating in the Grand Arena or Global Championship, understanding how to counter any team is crucial for success in Hero Wars Mobile. In this article, we will discuss three effective strategies that you must know to counter any opponent&amp;rsquo;s team. By implementing these strategies, you will be able to create a solid strategy for your own teams or heroes, ensuring victory in every battle.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Abusing the Power of Sw Alicia: Queen of Cleaving</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/sw-alicia-runes/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/sw-alicia-runes/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss the Multiverse Arena Battle, featuring the incredible sw Alicia and the strategies to dominate the battlefield. Join us as we explore the exciting world of high-tier team battles and witness the power of the Queen of Cleaving.
Key Points:
Introduction to the Multiverse Arena Battle The Challenge of the Billionaire Server The Queen of Cleaving: Introducing sw Alicia Investing in Devilmon for sw Alicia Exploring the Unique Abilities of sw Alicia The Ultimate Death Knight: Breaking News from Rage Shadow Legends The Death Knight Hunt Event: Get the Ultimate Death Knight for Free Using the Promo Code DK Rises in Rage Shadow Legends Battle Strategies and Team Compositions Analyzing the Speed and Rune Requirements The Unexpected Challenges in the Arena Battle The Power of Cleaving: A Unique Approach to Arena Battles Adjusting the Strategy with Tiana Dealing with the Speed Team: A Cleaving Change An Artful Defense: The Dedication of Opponents Strategies for Free-to-Play Players: Replacing Xyros Facing Adversity: Overcoming Difficulties The Ultimate Test: The Doom of Uncertainty Introduction to the Multiverse Arena Battle The Multiverse Arena Battle is a thrilling competition in which teams battle it out for supremacy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Epic Seven Hell Raid: Yufine&#39;s Counter Cheese Strategy for an Efficient Clear</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-hell-raid-map/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/epic-seven-hell-raid-map/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In a recent update, Epic Seven revamped their raid system, making it more challenging and time-consuming. One major change is that now, if you leave the raid, all the mobs reset, and you have to fight them again upon re-entry. This means that clearing the raid requires multiple entries and can be quite tedious. However, there is a strategy that allows you to clear the entire Hell Raid in just one entry.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Idle Heroes - Can Horus Carry In SL 23&#43;???</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/idle-heroes-horus-build/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/idle-heroes-horus-build/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will be discussing the viability of Horus, one of the heroes in the game Idle Heroes, in Shadow Sea Land. We will explore whether Horus can carry a team to victory in SL 23 or higher. We will also discuss the hero lineup, gear, and artifacts needed for optimal performance.
Introduction
Shadow Sea Land, or SL, is a challenging game mode in Idle Heroes where players progress through various levels by defeating waves of enemies.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> King&#39;s Raid - Ultimate Runes Guide: Where to Get and How to Use Them</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/mediana-runes-kings-raid/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 21 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/mediana-runes-kings-raid/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: In this comprehensive guide, we will explore the world of runes in King&amp;rsquo;s Raid. Runes play a crucial role in enhancing your heroes&amp;rsquo; abilities and improving their performance in battles. So, let&amp;rsquo;s dive into the world of runes and learn everything you need to know about acquiring and utilizing them effectively.
Where to Get Runes: Before we delve into the details of rune acquisition, it&amp;rsquo;s important to note that the best runes in King&amp;rsquo;s Raid are the ancient runes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Gems of War Warlord Class Trial: Fast and Easy Team Strategy</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/class-trial-gems-of-war/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/class-trial-gems-of-war/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this article, we will discuss a fast and easy team strategy for the Warlord class trial in Gems of War. We will provide step-by-step instructions on how to assemble and use the team effectively. Additionally, we will review the rewards and weapons available in the class trial.
Key Points Warlord Class Trial Rewards Available Troops for the Team Recommended Weapon: Black Manacles Team Formation Banner Choice: Hive Banner Battle Strategy Using Manacles and Black Manacles for Devour Utilizing Ogres and Gog and God for Magic Based Damage Stone Giant for Mana Generation Progressing through the Class Trial Collecting Rewards Warlord Class Trial Rewards Before we dive into the team strategy, let&amp;rsquo;s discuss the rewards and weapons available in the Warlord class trial.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> How to Maximize Your Gem Spending in Raid: Shadow Legends</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/best-way-to-spend-gems-raid-shadow-legends/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/best-way-to-spend-gems-raid-shadow-legends/</guid>
      <description>Introduction: Welcome to this comprehensive guide on how to properly spend your gems in Raid: Shadow Legends! In this article, we will delve into the best strategies to upgrade your gem economy, avoid common mistakes, and optimize your gameplay. Whether you are a beginner or a late-game player, these tips will help you make the most out of your gem investments. So let&amp;rsquo;s get started!
Gem Mine: The Foundation for Success The first thing you should prioritize is the Gem Mine.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Save Gold Orbs &amp; Blitz Credits - Review of Upcoming Events in Marvel Strike Force</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/msf-blitz-credits/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/msf-blitz-credits/</guid>
      <description>Introduction
In this video, we will discuss the upcoming events in Marvel Strike Force and the strategies to maximize your rewards. We will cover the importance of saving your gold orbs, earning alliance credits, and hoarding blitz credits. Additionally, we will touch upon the community&amp;rsquo;s demand for a trade-in system and the concerns regarding certain characters in the game. Finally, we will review some in-game offers that are currently available.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> The Complete Guide to Ghazghkull - The New Orc Guild Raid Boss: Gameplay, Traits, and Best Characters to Use</title>
      <link>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-guild-raid/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://game-loid.github.io/posts/kings-raid-guild-raid/</guid>
      <description>Guild raids in King&amp;rsquo;s Raid are always a source of excitement for players, and the addition of the new orc leader Ghazghkull has taken it to a whole new level. Known as one of the most influential orcs in the Warhammer 40,000 Universe, Ghazghkull is a formidable boss that has fought against various factions including the Imperium, Eldari, Chaos, and Necrons. In this guide, we will take an in-depth look at Ghazghkull, his skills, traits, and discuss which characters are good or bad against him.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
